Guide to the Alpha Delta Phi Records, 1832 - 2017
Alpha Delta Phi Records 1832 - 2017
- Series VIII: Members, 1852-2011
  - Personal Papers
    - Flannigan, E. Jenny K.
      - Finance
        - Annual Drive Letters, 1993-1996 (Box 112, Folder 2)
        - 1996 (Box 112, Folder 3)
        - Fundraising, Mailings to Members, 1996-1997 (Box 112, Folder 4)
        - Finances & Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 112, Folder 5-6)
        - 1999-2000 (Box 112, Folder 7)
        - Evie's House, 2000 (Box 112, Folder 8)
        - 2000-2002 (Box 112, Folder 9-10)
      - House & Property
        - 1992 (Box 112, Folder 11)
        - 1993-1996 (Box 113, Folder 1-4)
        - Dorm furniture, 1995-1996 (Box 113, Folder 5)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 113, Folder 6)
        - Leather couches, 1998 (Box 113, Folder 7)
        - 1999-2000 (Box 113, Folder 8)
        - Furniture & Curtains - Living Room, 1999-2000 (Box 113, Folder 9)
        - 2000-2001 (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Greene Room Fire Egress, 2001-2002 (Box 113, Folder 11)
      - Star & Crescent
        - 1996-1999 (Box 113, Folder 12-15)
        - 2000-2002 (Box 114, Folder 1-2)
      - Society
        - 1st Annual Convention, 1993 (Box 114, Folder 3-4)
        - Board of Governors, 1993-1995 (Box 114, Folder 5)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 114, Folder 6)
        - Constitution, 1998 (Box 114, Folder 7)
        - Misc., 1998 (Box 114, Folder 8)
        - 1999-2000 (Box 114, Folder 9)
        - Board of Governors Meeting, 2000 June (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Gershen, Robert D.1975-2013
      - ADP charge (Box 114, Folder 11)
      - AEF
        - Correspondence, 2006-2013 (Box 114, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence, 1987-2004 (Box 115, Folder 1-6)
        - Finance Committee, 2005-2013 (Box 115, Folder 7-8)
        - Finance Committee, 1997-2004 (Box 116, Folder 1-2)
        - Meetings, 2008-2013 (Box 116, Folder 3-9)
        - Meetings, 1997-2007 (Box 117, Folder 1-7)
        - Meetings, 1985-1996 (Box 118, Folder 1-6)
        - Summer Work Study account, 1984 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - ALS
        - Correspondence, 1995-2009 (Box 118, Folder 8-11)
        - Correspondence, 1976-1994 (Box 119, Folder 1-4)
        - Finance Committee, 1998 June-2010 (Box 119, Folder 5-8)
        - Finance Committee, 1982-1998 June (Box 120, Folder 1-7)
        - Leases between ALS & undergraduate chapter (Box 120, Folder 8)
        - Meetings, 1998-2008 (Box 120, Folder 9-10)
        - Meetings, 1975-1997 (Box 121, Folder 1-7)
      - Correspondence
        - Gershen/McKelvey, 1994-2010 (Box 121, Folder 8-11)
        - Gershen/McKelvey, 1984-1993 (Box 122, Folder 1-3)
      - Evelyn Kowaleski (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - House & property, 1984 Renovation (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - International (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - Society, 1997-2005 (Box 122, Folder 7-11)
      - Society, 1993-1996 (Box 123, Folder 1-3)
      - Wesleyan, 1994-2009 (Box 123, Folder 4-7)
      - Audio-Visual Materials
        - Interview with Tracy Winn '75, 1989 April 10 (Box 124, Folder 1)
          Contains cassette tape.
        - Alpha Delta Phi Panel Discussion, 1998 May 29 (Box 124, Folder 2)
        - Foregone Conclusion, 1991 (Box 124, Folder 3)
        - Alpha Delta Phi Celebrates Cultural History, 2004 May 22 (Box 124, Folder 4-5)
    - Konerding, Erhard
      - ALS
        - Board Committees (Box 123, Folder 8)
        - Board Lists (Box 123, Folder 9)
      - Chapter
        - Directories (Box 123, Folder 10)
        - Officers (Box 123, Folder 11)
        - Pledge manuals (Box 123, Folder 12)
      - Newspaper clippings (Box 123, Folder 13)
      - Personal (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - Oversize, poster (Box 207)
      - Scholarship (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - Songbooks (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - Misc. ADP stuff (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Kowalski, Carl & Evelyn
      - Evie (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - Oversize, scrapbook (Box 208)
    - McKelvey, Robert G.
      Robert G. McKelvey became president of the ALS in 1971 and of the AEF in 1974. The ALS and the AEF had functionally collapsed into one organization. This situation threatened the tax-exempt status of the AEF. The late 1960s and early 1970s were restless times at Wesleyan and the chapter was affected. The files cover a make or break period of the chapter's history.
      - AEF
        - Articles of Association and By-Laws (Box 125, Folder 6)
        - Trust Agreement & Minutes (Box 125, Folder 7)
        - Administrative Expenses (Box 125, Folder 8)
        - Assembly Series, 1974-1975 (Box 125, Folder 9)
        - Endowment, [1972-1973] (Box 125, Folder 10)
        - Grant Procedure, Change in 1975-76 Budget (Box 125, Folder 11)
        - Portfolio Review, 1977 (Box 125, Folder 12)
        - Portfolio Review, 1975 May 23 (Box 125, Folder 13)
      - RGM Chronological Files ALS/AEF
        - 1971-9174 (Box 126, Folder 1-12)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 127, Folder 1-12)
      - RGM Correspondence
        - General, 1972-1978 (Box 128, Folder 1-3)
        - House, 1972-1981 (Box 128, Folder 4-9)
        - Renovations, 1974 (Box 128, Folder 10)
      - AEF
        The files below were accessioned at a later date from the initial accession of records. These files were created or collected during McKelvey's time as AEF President from 1971-2015, span from 1884-2015 and have been kept in original order of alphabetical and chronological arrangement.
        - Academic Dining, 1995-2002 (Box 128, Folder 11)
        - Accountant, 1978-2005 (Box 129, Folder 1)
        - Adelphic Aid, 1976-2005 (Box 129, Folder 2-6)
        - AdLit - Content summaries (File Note), 1960-1989 (Box 129, Folder 7)
        - AdLit - Funding & Correspondence, 1979-2001 (Box 129, Folder 8)
        - Archives - Bowdoin, 2004 (Box 129, Folder 9)
        - Assembly Series - Summaries of programs, 1884-1891, 1955-2005 (Box 129, Folder 10)
        - Assembly Series - Correspondence, Grants, 1975-1996 (Box 129, Folder 11-12)
        - Assembly Series - Correspondence, Grants, 2000-2009 (Box 130, Folder 1-3)
        - ASF - Association of Small Foundations, 1997-2011 (Box 130, Folder 4)
        - Bank Correspondence - general, 1975-1997 (Box 130, Folder 5-7)
        - Biddle Correspondence - RGM Archives (Box 130, Folder 8)
        - Boardroom/Archives
          - Renovation & Historic Preservation - Overview/Summary (File Note), 1977-2003 (Box 130, Folder 9)
          - Creation - 1977-1978, Lease to 2012 (Box 130, Folder 10)
          - Repair & Renovation, 1995-1998, Lease Extension to 2018 (Box 130, Folder 11-12)
          - Upgrade to Archival Standard, 1999-2000 (Box 130, Folder 13)
          - Upgrade to Archival Standard, 2001-2003 (Box 131, Folder 1-2)
          - Expansion for Sesquicentennial, 2003 (Box 131, Folder 3)
          - Preservation of documents, pictures & books, 1974-2009 (Box 131, Folder 4-7)
        - Budgets, 1976-2002 (Box 131, Folder 8)
        - Butterfield Luncheon
          - Guest List & Names (Box 131, Folder 9)
          - Butterfield Panel & Luncheon - Lifetime of Learning (File Note), 2002 May (Box 131, Folder 10)
          - Reception/Luncheon (Box 131, Folder 11)
          - untitled (Box 131, Folder 12)
          - Correspondence (Box 132, Folder 1-2)
        - Chandelier Restoration, 2002 (Box 132, Folder 3)
        - Coffeehouse, 1992-2005 (Box 132, Folder 4)
        - Community Service, 1993-2003 (Box 132, Folder 5)
        - Computer/Cable Wiring - Wireless installation & upgrade (File Note), 1990-2004 (Box 132, Folder 6)
        - Computer Auxiliary Equipment, 2003 (Box 132, Folder 7)
        - Connecticut State - all, 1984-2005 (Box 132, Folder 8)
        - Connecticut State - Sales tax Exemption, 1977 (Box 132, Folder 9)
        - Cornell Adelphic Education Fund, 1988-1998 (Box 132, Folder 10)
        - Davison, George, 1953,1990 (Box 132, Folder 11)
        - Eclectic Reorganization, 2010 (Box 132, Folder 12)
        - Expenses - Miscellaneous, 1978-2005 (Box 132, Folder 13)
        - Faculty Fellows, 1979-1998 (Box 132, Folder 14)
        - File Notes - all (Box 132, Folder 15)
        - Film Series (ADP), 1986-2005 (Box 133, Folder 1)
        - Founding Documents, originals & copies, 1944-[1997] (Box 133, Folder 2)
        - Grants
          - Summaries of Grant Procedures (File Note), 1993, 2002 (Box 133, Folder 3)
          - 1975-1982 (Box 133, Folder 4-9)
          - (no information see 1984 Budget), 1982-1983 (Box 133, Folder 10)
          - Summary, 1980-1984 (Box 133, Folder 11)
          - 1985-2002 (Box 133, Folder 12-28)
          - 2002-2009 (Box 134, Folder 1-11)
        - Greene, Richard, 1979-1984 (Box 134, Folder 12)
        - History
          - History of the AEF History - (with some ALS) (File Note) (Box 134, Folder 13)
          - AEF, Gershen, 1974-1975; 1997 (Box 134, Folder 14)
          - M. Biddle - Halls, Houses & Eating Clubs, 2004 (Box 135, Folder 1)
          - McKelvey (mostly includes ALS)mid 1970s & 2006 (Box 135, Folder 2)
          - AEF - 1979 - Reid [Read], Jeffway, Jeffers - 1979 (File Note) (Box 135, Folder 3)
          - Swain, late 1960s (Box 135, Folder 4)
          - AEF, Dhanda Correspondence, 1992-1997 (Box 135, Folder 5-6)
          - AEF - Dhanda Drafts (Box 135, Folder 7-9)
          - AEF - Sesquicentennial - Banquet speeches: Potts & others, 2006 (Box 135, Folder 10)
          - AEF - Sesquintennial - Alumni Oral History, 2006 (Box 135, Folder 11)
        - Insurance, D & O, 1993-2011 (Box 135, Folder 12)
        - IRS
          - Correspondence (Box 135, Folder 13-14)
          - Exemption Letter - Confirming 1949 original, 1993 (Box 136, Folder 1)
          - First Audit, 1972-1974 (Box 136, Folder 2)
          - Second Audit, 1983 (Box 136, Folder 3)
          - Tax Returns, 1977-2005 (Box 136, Folder 4-9)
        - Johnston, Albert - Notes & Obituary, (1952) (Box 136, Folder 10)
        - Leases (with ALS), 1977, 1998 (Box 136, Folder 11)
        - Library, 1979-2005 (Box 136, Folder 12)
        - Lifetime of Learning (File Note), 1998-2001 (Box 137, Folder 1-2)
        - Meetings
          - Summary & File Note (Box 137, Folder 3)
          - Jt. Meeting with ALS, 1970-1971 (Box 137, Folder 4-5)
          - 1972-1990 (Box 137, Folder 6-24)
          - 1991-2003 (Box 138, Folder 1-13)
          - Annual & Special, 2004 (Box 139, Folder 1-2)
          - 2005-2009 (Box 139, Folder 3-9)
          - Annual, 2010 (Box 139, Folder 10)
          - Retreat (File Note), 2010 (Box 139, Folder 11)
          - Retreat - Planning, 2010 May (Box 140, Folder 1-3)
          - Retreat - Meetings/Seminars, 2010 May (Box 140, Folder 4)
          - Retreat - Expenses, 2010 May (Box 140, Folder 5-7)
          - Retreat - Follow-up, 2010 May (Box 140, Folder 8)
        - Membership List (File Note), 1981, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 9)
        - Memos to Members & Board (File Note), 1988-2008 (Box 140, Folder 10-11)
        - Music Series, 1979-2005 (Box 141, Folder 1-2)
        - Notes & Mortgages (File Note) (Box 141, Folder 3)
        - Notes & Mortgages, 1974-2005 (Box 141, Folder 4-8)
        - Officers List (Box 141, Folder 9)
        - Poetry/Literature/Prose Series, 1980-2002 (Box 141, Folder 10)
        - Portfolio Correspondence, 1974-1989 (Box 141, Folder 11-12)
        - Portfolio Correspondence, 1990-2004 (Box 142, Folder 1)
        - Prizes - (Gram- Swain), 1989-2006 (Box 142, Folder 2)
        - Psi U Communications, 1997-2010 (Box 142, Folder 3)
        - Science Series, 1997-1998 (Box 142, Folder 4)
        - Statements
          - File Note (Box 142, Folder 5)
          - UBT, 1975-1987 (Box 142, Folder 6-8)
          - Fleet, 1988-1996 (Box 142, Folder 9-12)
          - Fleet, 1996-1998 (Box 143, Folder 1)
          - GMCO, 2002-2008 (Box 143, Folder 2-10)
          - GMCO, 2009-2010 (Box 144, Folder 1-2)
        - Theater, (P.J. Adler), 1989-2003 (Box 144, Folder 3)
        - Wesleyan
          - Alumni Fund (WAF) Summary, 1959-1994 (Box 144, Folder 4)
          - Alumni Fund (WAF) Gifts & correspondence, 1979-[2003] (Box 144, Folder 5)
          - Bennet Papers, 2009 (Box 144, Folder 6)
          - Wesleyan Challenge, 1993-1997 (Box 144, Folder 7-8)
          - Choral Music & Glee Club (tape) - Winslow, 1990-1992 (Box 144, Folder 9)
          - Film Series, 1994-1997 (Box 144, Folder 10)
          - History - Vol. II - Potts
            - File Note (Box 144, Folder 11)
            - Departure (after Vol. I), 1990 [1989]-1994 (Box 144, Folder 12)
            - Reengagement & Contract, 1999-2000 (Box 144, Folder 13)
            - Donor Solicitations & Communications, 2000-2015 (Box 144, Folder 14)
            - Donor Solicitations & Communications, 2000-2015 (Box 145, Folder 1-2)
            - Early Drafts & Critiques (Box 145, Folder 3-5)
            - Finances with Wesleyan, 2000-2015 (Box 145, Folder 6-10)
            - DP - RM Correspondence, 2000-2015 (Box 145, Folder 11)
            - DP - RM Correspondence, 2000-2015 (Box 146, Folder 1-2)
            - Author Reception (Box 146, Folder 3)
          - Olin Library Conservation Lab, Fume Hood, 2002-2003 (Box 146, Folder 4)
          - Olin Library Conservation Lab, Expansion, 2007-2009 (Box 146, Folder 5)
          - Trustee, Alpha Delts (to 1972) (Box 146, Folder 6)
          - Wesleyan Sings CD, 2007-2008 (Box 146, Folder 7-8)
            Contains CD.
          - Wesleyan Sings Jibers & Glee Club, [2007-2008] (Box 146, Folder 9)
        - Wesleyan Writers Conference, 1977-2006 (Box 146, Folder 10-12)
        - Wesleyan Writers Conference Brochures - various years, 1978-2011 [2007] (Box 146, Folder 13-14)
    - Polin, Jane
      The records of Jane Polin '80 are from her undergraduate years as chairman on different committees for the Chapter, with a small amount of material from post graduate years as a board member of the ALS. The records range from 1978-1986.
      - Chapter, 1979-1980 (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - Co-education Issue, 1982-1986 (Box 147, Folder 2)
      - Piano Drive, 1978-1979 (Box 147, Folder 3)
      - Telethon, 1978 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Spencer, Donald
      The records of Don Spencer '77 cover his time as ALS President from 1994-1996 with a small amount of material from later years as a board member of the ALS. The records range from 1977-1999.
      - ALS Meeting, 1995-1996 (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - AEF Loan to ALS, 1995-1996 (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - Alumni Correspondence, 1994-1999 (Box 147, Folder 7)
      - Chapter - ALS Leases, 1977 & 1994 (Box 147, Folder 8)
      - Chapter - Officers Lists, 1994-1996 (Box 147, Folder 9)
      - Wesleyan Dining Services Agreement, 1994 (Box 147, Folder 10)
      - Fundraising, 1994-1995 (Box 147, Folder 11)
      - House & Property Renovations, 1994-1995 (Box 147, Folder 12)
      - Wesleyan Loan to ALS, 1995 April (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Steffensen, James L.
      The records of James L. Steffenson cover his time serving in a variety of capacities such as board member of the ALS, Chairman of the Scholarship Committee, and Faculty Advisor to the House. The records range from 1974-1980 and are arranged in reverse chronological order.
      - Correspondence (Box 147, Folder 14)
      - Robert McKelvey (Box 147, Folder 15)
      - Trustees Material, 1975-1976 (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - Trustees Material, 1974-1975 & earlier (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Wasch, William Karl
      Bill Wasch '52 became Secretary of the ALS in 1984 and Secretary of the AEF in 1988, though he had been a member of both organizations' boards since the late 1960s. He later became the Treasurer of both the ALS and AEF. He has been Secretary/Treasurer for a significant portion of both organizations' histories, so his files cover a wide variety of events. These files include the transformation of the Society as it broke away from the Fraternity, the monumental debt reduction campaigns of the early 1990s and the financial struggles of the Star & Crescent throughout that decade. These files span from 1944-2007 and are arranged in alphabetical and chronological order.
      - AEF
        - Correspondence, 1969-1975 (Box 148, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence, 1980-1997 (Box 148, Folder 4-13)
        - Correspondence, 1998-2006 (Box 149, Folder 1-7)
        - Finance Committee, 1999-2007 (Box 149, Folder 8-10)
        - Minutes, 1944, 1969-1975 (Box 149, Folder 11)
        - Minutes, 1984-1993 (Box 149, Folder 12-15)
        - Minutes, 1994-2007 (Box 150, Folder 1-13)
        - Scholarship, 1969-1975 (Box 151, Folder 1)
        - Scholarship, 1987-2001 (Box 151, Folder 2-11)
        - Taxes, 1991-1992, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 12)
      - ALS
        - Correspondence, 1965-1984 May (Box 151, Folder 13-17)
        - Correspondence, 1984 June-1989 (Box 152, Folder 1-12)
        - Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 153, Folder 1-11)
        - Correspondence, 1995-2007 (Box 154, Folder 1-12)
        - Evelyn Kowaleski Estate, 1992-1994, 1999 (Box 154, Folder 13)
        - Expenses, 1984-1998 (Box 154, Folder 14-15)
        - Fundraising, 1983 [1984]-1985 (Box 155, Folder 1-3)
        - Fundraising - Checks, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 4)
        - Fundraising, 1986 (Box 155, Folder 5-6)
        - Fundraising - Checks, 1986 (Box 155, Folder 7-8)
        - Fundraising, 1987 (Box 155, Folder 9-10)
        - Fundraising - Checks, 1987 (Box 155, Folder 11)
        - Fundraising, 1988 (Box 155, Folder 12)
        - Fundraising - Checks, 1988 (Box 156, Folder 1)
        - Fundraising, 1989 (Box 156, Folder 2-4)
        - Fundraising - Checks, 1989 (Box 156, Folder 5-6)
        - Fundraising, 1990 (pt. 1) (Box 156, Folder 7-9)
        - Fundraising, 1990 (pt. 2) (Box 156, Folder 10-11)
        - Fundraising, 1990 (pt. 2) (Box 157, Folder 1)
        - Fundraising - Checks, 1990 (Box 157, Folder 2-3)
        - Fundraising, 1991 (Box 157, Folder 4-5)
        - Fundraising - Checks, 1991 (Box 157, Folder 6)
        - Fundraising, 1992 (Box 157, Folder 7-9)
        - Fundraising, 1993 (Box 157, Folder 10)
        - Fundraising - Checks, 1993 (Box 157, Folder 11)
        - Fundraising, 1994 (Box 157, Folder 12)
        - Fundraising - Checks, 1994 (Box 158, Folder 1)
        - Fundraising, 1995 (Box 158, Folder 2)
        - Fundraising - Checks, 1995 (Box 158, Folder 3)
        - Fundraising, 1996-1997 (Box 158, Folder 4)
        - Fundraising - Checks, 1996 (Box 158, Folder 5)
        - Fundraising, 1999 (Box 158, Folder 6)
        - Fundraising, 2004-2006 (Box 158, Folder 7)
        - Insurance, 1982-1994 (Box 158, Folder 8-13)
        - Insurance, 1995-2001 (Box 159, Folder 1-3)
        - Insurance - Misc., undated (Box 159, Folder 4)
        - Minutes, 1965-1972 (Box 159, Folder 5)
        - Minutes, 1983-1990 (Box 159, Folder 6-14)
        - Minutes, 1991-2004, 2006 (Box 160, Folder 1-15)
        - Taxes, 1945, 1984-1993 (Box 160, Folder 16-17)
      - Chapter - Composites (Box 161, Folder 1)
      - Co-Educational Issue, 1973-1994 (Box 161, Folder 2-3)
      - Correspondence
        - Wasch/McKelvey, 1970 [1974]-2007 (Box 161, Folder 4-14)
      - Housing
        - 1983-1986 (Box 162, Folder 1)
        - Boarder Statements, 1985-1990 (Box 162, Folder 2-4)
        - Room Lease Agreements, 1986-1990 (Box 162, Folder 5-7)
      - International
        - Convention, 1984-1985 (Box 162, Folder 8-10)
        - Convention, 1986-1988 (Box 163, Folder 1-4)
        - Convention, 1991 (Box 163, Folder 5)
        - Convention, 1993 (Box 163, Folder 6)
      - Society
        - Convention, 1995, 1999 (Box 163, Folder 7)
      - Wesleyan (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Yaus, Jeffrey
      The files of Jeffrey Yaus consist of records created or collected during his time as ALS President from 2002-2005. The records span from 1970-2005.
      - AEF, 2002-2005 (Box 163, Folder 9-10)
      - ADP History, 1970-2004 (Box 163, Folder 11)
      - ALS, 2002-2005 (Box 163, Folder 12)
      - ALS Meetings, 2002-2005 (Box 163, Folder 13)
      - Email
        - AEF (Box 163, Folder 14)
        - Alumni Relations - Annual Report (Box 163, Folder 15)
        - Alumni Relations - general (Box 163, Folder 16)
        - Alumni Relations - mailing lists (Box 163, Folder 17)
        - Chapter Relations (Box 164, Folder 1)
        - Finance (Box 164, Folder 2)
        - General, 2002 May-2005 May (Box 164, Folder 3-6)
        - House & Property, 2002 June-2005 (Box 164, Folder 7-10)
        - Society Convention, 2002-2003 (Box 164, Folder 11)
        - Star & Crescent, 2002-2005 (Box 165, Folder 1-3)
      - House & Property, 2002-2004 (Box 165, Folder 4)
      - Society, 2003 (Box 165, Folder 5)
      - Star & Crescent, 2005 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Yuhas, Eric
      The files of Eric Yuhas '88 consist of records created or collected during his time as Chapter House Manager, Treasurer and President, with the earlier records possibly passed on by previous presidents. The records span from 1978-1988.
      - AEF, 1979-1986 (Box 165, Folder 7)
      - ALS
        - Contact sheets (Box 165, Folder 8)
        - House correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 165, Folder 9)
        - Memos, 1974, 1983 (Box 165, Folder 10)
        - Minutes, 1981, 1985-1987 (Box 165, Folder 11)
        - Finances, 1981, 1984-1987 (Box 165, Folder 12)
      - [House]
        - Correspondence to Alums (Box 165, Folder 13)
        - Important General Info (Box 165, Folder 14)
        - ADP Annual Budgets (Box 165, Folder 15)
        - Billing, 1978, 1987-1988 (Box 165, Folder 16)
        - Board of House Presidents, 1986-1987 (Box 165, Folder 17)
        - Fire Dept., 1982, 1985-1986 (Box 165, Folder 18)
        - Health Dept., 1980-1987 (Box 165, Folder 19)
        - Initiation, 1986-1987 (Box 165, Folder 20)
        - Intrachapter In, 1986-1987 (Box 165, Folder 21)
        - Intrachapter Out, 1987 (Box 165, Folder 22)
        - House Insurance, 1980 (Box 165, Folder 23)
        - Lease, 1980, 1985 (Box 165, Folder 24)
        - Alumni Reimburstments [sic], 1983, 1986-1987 (Box 166, Folder 1)
        - Phi Survival Guide, 1987 (Box 166, Folder 2)
        - Reader/Writer Conference, 1982 (Box 166, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence - Wesleyan, 1982-1987 (Box 166, Folder 4)
        - Completed Space Contracts, 1987-1988 (Box 166, Folder 5)
        - Summer House (Box 166, Folder 6)
        - Thesis Binding (Box 166, Folder 7)
      - [International - Alpha Delta Phi]
        - Proposal to hold Convention, [1980-1983] (Box 166, Folder 8)
        - 146th Convention, Building A Strong Alumni Organization, 1978 (Box 166, Folder 9)
          The 1978 annual convention was hosted by the Middletown Chapter.
        - Correspondence (Box 166, Folder 10)
        - Visitation Reports (Box 166, Folder 11)
        - Contact Lists (Box 166, Folder 12)
        - Seward Scholarship (Box 166, Folder 13)
        - Sword & Spear (Box 166, Folder 14)
        - Literary Competition (Box 166, Folder 15)
        - Wesleyan Fraternities correspondence to International (Box 166, Folder 16)
  - Summaries
    - Summary Lists (Box 166, Folder 17)
  - Personal Realia
    - Burnham, Frederick Waters
      These items consist of a coffeepot and sugar pot and email correspondence between Frederick Burnham's grandson and Leslie Starr regarding the acquisition of those personal items, which belonged to Frederick, class of 1912, and his wife, Ramona Hubbard, and are believed to have been given as a gift from the ADP, Middletown Chapter.
      - Email correspondence, 2012 (Box 167, Folder 1)
      - Coffeepot & sugar pot, ca. 1913 (Box 168)
    - Eustis, John Edward
      These items consist of two pins and a brief typed biography of John Edward Eustis, class of 1874.
      - Brief biography on Eustis (Box 167, Folder 2)
      - ADP pin & rowing medal, 1874 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Littell, Frank Bowers